(Leonard:)So how you doing?
(Leslie:)-Fine. You?
-Not bad.
(Leonard:)You remember
when we used to have sex...
...and you said it didn't mean anything,
it was just for fun?
(Penny:)Yeah.
[STAMMERING]
Do you wanna do that again?
(Leslie:)What happened? Blondie dumped you?
(Leonard:)She didn't dump me. We were
just in different places in the relationship.
(Howard:)Right.
(Leonard:)Anyway, apparently, it's okay to go back
to people you're no longer seeing...
(Leonard:)-...and have recreational sex with them.
-Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)So, what do you say?
(Leslie:)Let me think about it.
(Leonard:)She's not coming back.
(Raj:)-Uh-oh. She wants to meet us.
-Not us. Him.
Yes, but "him"
doesn't even know about "her."
Well, "him" about to find out about "her."